

Elvis JinFull Stack Developer



Vancouver, BC, Canada

Over 8 years of experience delivering tech solutions. Avid programmer and fast learner. Obsessed with detail and quality. Always trying to improve development and communication processes. I love simple and elegant solutions for every problem.







Work Experience

Senior Web Developer • Inforox

December 2019 - October 2022



Designed the application architecture and built it using Typescript, React, Angular, and Nest.js. Mentored experienced developers who were new to Angular + Nest.js. Followed the Google Material Design and Fuse theme, while completing this project, contributed to the Fuse Theme as a contributor.

I also took the role as a DevOps as well, and I used AWS for hosting the web application using the services like route53, CloudFront, EC2 instances, Elastic load balancer, certificate manager and RDS for hosting the DBs. As a lead developer, I wrote the CI/CD pipelines for the automated deployment of staging and production servers using GitHub actions.

Full Stack Engineer • Web Maniac

December 2016 - July 2018



Also building Restful APIs using Node/Express.

Mostly performed automated testing tasks using Jest/Cypress.

And I was responsible for AWS Lambda, S3, EC2, and DynamoDB, CDK.

Junior Web Developer • Tsing hua

January 2014 - October 2016



While working there, I could have a good understanding of PHP, PHP Framework, Database, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, HTTP/URL, DOM, React and web browsers, at least.

The most important thing is that I was able to be a good communicator when it comes to leaving notes in the code for later use, writing progress reports for stakeholders and explaining project details to the team.

Education

2018 - 2019

British Columbia Institute of Technology, Vancouver, Cananda

Software Engineering

Tsinghua

Computer Science



Powered by CakeResume